yourfreesurveys.com 2014-04-03

# Your Free Survey

PRIVACY POLICY 

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices of Yesfree.com LLC ("Company") and all websites owned or operated by Company and its subsidiaries and corporate affiliates, including, but not limited to, yourfreesurveys.com and onlycashsurveys.com. Company (sometimes referred to herein as "us" or "we") collects your personal information for use in connection with the services Company provides. The following sections describe how your information is collected by us, and how we use such information. 

1\. ACCEPTANCE 

1.1           By using a Company website(s) and registering for Company services, you become subject to this privacy policy and the applicable Terms of Use, including for any dispute regarding privacy. **BY USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE APPLICABLE TERMS OF USE.**

1.2           If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to our websites and any other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of those changes. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. It is your responsibility to review the policy frequently in order to remain aware of any changes. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by other means, such as e-mail, at our sole discretion. Your continued use of any portion of our website following posting of the updated privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes. 

2\. INFORMATION COLLECTED 

2.1           Personal Information. When you register to use our services, we collect a variety of information about you. Generally, we use your information to tailor our services to you and send you the surveys most relevant to you. We reserve the right to disclose your contact information (name, mailing address, e-mail address, etc.) to third parties. However, we will keep strictly confidential all other information your provide us, including, without limitation, sexual preference, health information, and PayPal account information. 

2.2           Log Files. Any time you visit any of our websites, our servers automatically gather information from your browser (such as your IP addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks) to analyze trends, administer the site, prevent fraud, track visitor movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information. For example, we may log your IP address for system administration purposes. IP addresses are logged to track a userâ€™s session. We do not share the log files externally, and IP addresses are not linked to any personally identifiable information. 

2.3           Cookies. We use â€œcookiesâ€ to keep track of some types of information while you are visiting our website or using our services. Cookies are very small files placed on your computer, and they allow us to count the number of visitors to our website and distinguish repeat visitors from new visitors. They also allow us to save user preferences and track user trends. We rely on cookies for the proper operation of our website. Therefore, if your browser is set to reject all cookies, the website may not function properly. Users who refuse cookies assume all responsibility for any resulting loss of functionality. We do not link the cookies to any of your personal information. 

2.4           Web Beacons. â€œWeb beaconsâ€ (also known as â€œclear gifsâ€ and â€œpixel tagsâ€) are small transparent graphic images that are often used in conjunction with cookies in order to further personalize our website for our users and to collect a limited set of information about our visitors. We may also use web beacons in e-mail communications in order to understand the behavior of our customers. We do not link the web beacons to any personal information. 

2.5           E-mail Messages. We require an e-mail address from you when you register for our services. We use your e-mail for both transactional (e.g., notifying you when you have become eligible for payouts because of your credit level) and promotional (e.g., daily third-party offers) purposes. E-mail messages we send you may contain code that enables our database to track your usage of the e-mails, including whether the e-mail was opened and what links (if any) were clicked. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Company services, such as service announcements and administrative messages. By signing up for our services, you agree to receive our newsletter and offers to take surveys and other money making opportunities. If you do not wish to receive these e-mails, you may opt-out at any time, by clicking on the opt-out link in the e-mail messages you receive. 

3\. THIRD-PARTY DISCLOSURES 

3.1           Disclosure Required By Law. You acknowledge and agree that we may disclose information you provide, if required to do so by law, at the request of a third party, or if we, in our sole discretion, believe that disclosure is reasonable to (1) comply with the law, requests or orders from law enforcement, or any legal process (whether or not such disclosure is required by applicable law); (2) protect or defend Companyâ€™s, or a third partyâ€™s, rights or property; or (3) protect someoneâ€™s health or safety. 

3.2           Disclosure to Trusted Third Parties. You acknowledge and agree that we may share your contact information with certain selected third parties, so that these parties can send you daily offers of goods and services that we believe may be of interest to our users. This paragraph has no effect on our rights to use your information in connection with the provision of services through our websites. 

3.3           Your Disclosure to Trusted Third Parties. While visiting our site, we may provide you with advertisements, promotions, sweepstakes, and offers from third party providers. If you choose to accept any such offers, you may directly provide your information in connection with the offer to such third-party provider. Please refer to the third party providerâ€™s own privacy policy if you have any questions regarding how your information will be used by such providers. Please be aware that these offers may be presented on pages framed by a Company website. Although these offer pages have the look and feel of our websites, you will be submitting your information directly to the third-party advertiser. You agree that we will not be responsible or liable for any loss or damage of any sort incurred as the result of any such dealings or as the result of the presence of such providers on a Company site. 

4\. ADVERTISING 

4.1           We may use third-party advertising agencies or other service providers to serve ads on our website on behalf of Company or third-party advertisers (e.g., retailers of goods or services). These companies may employ cookies and web beacons to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect through the use of cookies and web beacons is completely anonymous. 

5\. OPTING OUT 

5.1           Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to us in an e-mail (at the address provided below) with "unsubscribe" in the subject line of the e-mail, or e-mail us at [support@yesfree.com.](mailto:support@yesfree.com) (Some sites are able to offer opt-out mechanisms on member information pages and also supply a telephone or postal option as a way to opt-out.) 

6\. AGE REQUIREMENTS 

6.1           Our age restrictions for different services are set forth in the applicable Terms of Use. We do not target our sites or services to children under the age of 13, and in compliance with the Childrenâ€™s Online Privacy Protection Act, any information we may receive from users we believe to be under the age of 13 will be purged from our database. 

7\. SECURITY MEASURES 

7.1           We have put in place certain security measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information stored in our database. We will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers, but given that no information transmitted over the Internet can be guaranteed completely secure, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet and hence accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure. 

8\. LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES 

8.1           We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices or the content of any other websites that may provide access to, or be linked to or from, our websites, including that of any third party advertisers whose offerings require you to navigate away from our websites. 

9\. MISCELLANEOUS 

9.1           Contact Us. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with any Company websites, you can contact [ customerservice@yesfree.com](mailto:customerservice@yesfree.com). 

9.2           Last Update. This Agreement was last revised on March 9, 2011. 

* * *
